Guide to the Brooklyn schools collection CBHM.0006
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 2: Individual schools
  - Brooklyn Evening High School
    - Pegasus yearbook, 1933 June (Box 3)
      Gift of Richard Cantu.
  - Brooklyn Female Academy
    - Messenger Bird yearbook, 1849-1850 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Brooklyn Friends School
    - Catalogs, 1886-1887, 1913-1914, 1923-1924 (Box 3)
    - Class photograph, circa 1921-1922 (Folder Flat File)
      Gift of Georgette Love.
    - Friends School yearbook, 1929, 1930 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Friends School Life, 1932 June (Box 3)
      "An annual published by the pupils." Commencement issue.
    - Life yearbook, 1934, 1936 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Blue and Gray, 1937, 1939 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Senior yearbook, 1938 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - The Life newspaper, 1952, 1967, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Image, 1960, 1962 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - List of parent teacher club officers and chairmen, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - Student protest flyer, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Minutes journal, 1975-1989 (Box 3)
    - Promotional booklet and pamphlets, circa 1980s (Box 3)
    - Brooklyn Friends yearbook, 1985, 1986, 2013, 2016 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Eighth grade celebration program, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Fundraising mailing, 1993 (Box 3)
    - bfs newsletter, 1993-1995 (Box 15)
  - Brooklyn Heights Montessori School
    - Press release, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Heights Seminary
    - Catalogs, 1852-1882, 1887-1892, 1908-1909, 1911-1912, 1916-1920 (Box 3)
    - Alonzo Gray Address on Female Education, 1854 (Box 3)
    - Commencement invitation, 1910 (Box 3)
    - Commencement program, 1913 (Box 3)
    - The Triangle publication, 1913, 1915, 1920 (Box 3)
    - Club booklets, 1920-1921, 1925-1926 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn High School
    - Circular, 1849 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn High School of Automotive Trades
    - Headlight yearbook, 1938, 1944, 1945, 1948 (Box 4, Volume Library gallery shelf)
      One of the 1944 yearbooks was the gift of Michael Borkan, 2025. The other 1944 yearbook and the 1945 yearbook were the gift of Glenn Rosenblum.
    - Press kit, 1953 (Box 4)
    - Student reflections document (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn High School of Women's Garment Trades
    - Commencement program, 1939 (Box 4)
      Gift of Richard McHugh.
  - Brooklyn Hospital School of Nursing
    - Starch and Stripes yearbook, 1957 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Brooklyn Juvenile High School
    - Catalogs, 1855, 1866-1870, 1874 (Box 4)
    - Event program, 1868 (Box 4)
    - Declamation card, 1869 (Box 4)
    - Report card, 1881 (Box 14)
  - Brooklyn Latin School
    - Catalog, 1899-1900 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Law School
    - Commencement programs, 1903, 1910, 1913 (Box 4)
    - Bulletin, 1903-1904, 1930-1931, 1972-1972 (Box 4)
    - Anouncement [catalog], 1955-1956 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Maternity and New York State School for Training Nurses
    - Annual meeting program, 1890 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Music School
    - Promotional booklets, 1957-1958, 1973-1974, 1984-1985, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Music School Settlement
    - Annual reports, 1910-1914 (Box 4)
    - Pamphlet, 1914 (Box 4)
    - Year Book, 1918, 1919 (Box 4)
    - Event program, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Normal School for Physical Training
    - Catalog, 1886 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Post-Graduate Medical School
    - Catalogs, 1907, 1909 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Preparatory School
    - Catalogs, 1887-1888, 1890-1891 (Box 4)
    - Football team season ticket, 1922 (Box 4)
    - The Blue Book yearbook, 1929, 1931, 1940-1943 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - The Brooklyn Prep magazine, 1952-1953, 1955, 1956 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn School for Music and Theatre
    - "A School Grows in Brooklyn" article, circa 2000s (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Technical High School
    - Commencement ticket, 1923 (Box 4)
    - Survey yearbook, 1925-1932 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      June 1925, January 1928, January 1929, January 1930, January 1931, January 1932
    - Senior promenade program, 1926 (Box 4)
    - Blueprint yearbook, 1933-2006 (Volume Library gallery shelf, Box 4)
      1937 copy transferred from the Bronx County Historical Society.
      June 1933, January & June 1934, June 1935, June 1936, January & June 1937, January & June 1938, January 1939, January & June 1941, January & June 1942, January & June 1943, January 1945, January 1946, June 1947, June 1948, January 1949, January 1950, January 1951, January 1952, January 1953, January 1954, January 1955, January 1957, January & June 1958, January 1959, January 1960, 1961-1965, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1977-1982, 1984-1994, 1996-2006
    - Commencement programs, 1946-1948, 2013 (Box 4)
    - Service squad card, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Event programs, 2000, 2012 (Box 4)
      Gift of Liz Sciabarra.
    - Alumni Association report, 2001 (Box 4)
    - Career Day booklet, 2013 (Box 4)
    - The Radish satirical newsletter, 2013 (Box 4)
  - Brooklyn Training School
    - Alumni business card, circa early 20th century (Box 4)
  - Browne's Brooklyn Business College
    - Promotional materials, circa 1909 (Box 4)
  - Bryant and Stratton Business College
    - Catalogs, 1885, 1887 (Box 4)
  - Bushwick High School
    - Concert program, 1919 (Box 4)
    - Bushwick Beacon yearbook, 1915 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement programs, 1922, 1967 (Box 4)
    - Senior Year Book, June 1925, January 1929, January 1930 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Oriole yearbook, 1940-1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1943 copy was the gift of Joanne Canapary Stopka.
      January 1940, 1943, January 1944, January 1946, 1947, 1955, 1959, 1960-1968
    - Books for You reading list, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 4)
    - Drummer yearbook, 1983 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - The C.F. Young School
    - Promotional booklet, circa 1940s (Box 4)
  - Caldwell Institute
    - Catalog, circa 1845-1846 (Box 4)
      Gift of Mr. D. Gilman.
  - Canarsie High School
    - Looking Glass yearbook, 1963-2010 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1963, 1977-1979, 1981-1986, 1990, 1992-1995, 1998, 2000-2002, 2004, 2010
    - Diploma, 1972 (Box 5)
      Berlinda Jones. Also includes Jones's J.H.S. diploma, 1969, which does not specify a school.
    - Canarsie: History of a Growing Community student publication, 1976 (Box 5)
      Inscribed by Vesta Campbell.
  - Catherine McAuley Commercial High School
    - Mercian yearbook, 1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      Gift of St. Augustine's Diocesan High School.
  - Cathedral College (of the Immaculate Conception)
    - Commencement programs and invitation, 1946, 1947, 1950 (Box 5)
    - Cathedral Annual yearbook, 1940, 1941, 1946, 1947, 1950, 1951 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Yearbook, 1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Clara Barton Vocational High School / High School for Health Professions
    - Bartonian yearbook, June 1959, June 1962, 1970, 1984 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1970 and 1984 yearbooks were the gift of Alice Browne, 2022.
  - Clinton Avenue Institute
    - Circular, circa 1870s-1880s (Box 5)
  - Club Kindergarten School
    - Class photograph, 1926 (Box 5)
      Gift of Elaine Harmon.
  - Colby Academy
    - Pamphlet, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 5)
  - College Grammar School
    - Catalogs, 1868, 1870, undated (Box 5)
  - Columbian Institute
    - Catalog, 1876-1877 (Box 5)
  - Commercial High School (Alexander Hamilton High School)
    Historical Note
    The Commercial High School was organized in 1899 as an offshoot of Boys' High School, which was itself an offshoot of Brooklyn's Central Grammar School, established 1878. In 1925 the school was renamed the Alexander Hamilton High School of Commerce. The school closed in 1942, and is separate from Alexander Hamilton Vocational High School.
    - The Ledger magazine, 1906-1908, 1913 April-June (Box 19)
      The 1906-1908 issues were the gift of Andrea Mather-Stow, 2025.
    - Commencement program, 1937 (Box 19)
    - Booklet with school history 1878-1942 (Box 19)
      One of the two copies was the gift of Miss Mabel Bartlett.
  - Community School
    - Scholarship fund benefit souvenir journal, 1944-1945, 1947-1950 (Box 5)
  - De Severinus Academy of Fine and Applied Arts
    - Catalog, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Dodworth's Dancing Academy
    - Event materials, circa 1859-1862 (Box 5)
    - Payment invoices, 1875, 1879 (Box 5)
    - Promotional booklet, 1878 (Box 5)
  - East Midwood Academy
    - Promotional booklet and flyer, 1958 (Box 5)
  - East Midwood Jewish Center
    - Sefer Hashonoh yearbook, 1939 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - East New York Vocational School
    - Crossroads yearbook, 1944-1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Eastern District High School
    - "Gift of Fire" mural postcard, 1919 (Box 5)
    - Mural painting unveiling program, 1922 (Box 5)
    - Eastern yearbook, 1936-1947 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      June 1936, June 1937, January 1943, January 1944, June 1945, January 1947.
      The June 1945 yearbook was the gift of Rita C. Carole, 2025.
      Custodial History
      The January 1944 yearbook belonged to Sonya Gendzier.
    - Diploma, 1937 (Box 5)
      Fred Muchnick. Has two pins and a badge attached.
    - Yvette "Yetta" Isaacs materials, 1937-1938 (Box 5)
      "E" patch, flower petals pressed in her yearbook, 1938 recommendation letters, 1937 athletics certificate.
    - Gold and White newspaper, 1938 (Box 15)
    - Martin Oper materials, 1940-1943 (Box 5)
      Honor roll cards (1941-1942), diploma (1943). Also includes a diploma from J.H.S. 49 (1940).
    - Sonya Gendzier materials, 1942-1944; 2025.039 (Box 5)
      Five report cards, two honor roll certificates, commencement program and commencement dinner program, and one photograph. These materials also came with three pieces of Japanese currency the relevance of which is unknown. Gendzier's 1944 yearbook is shelved with the other yearbooks from the school.
      Transfer from Jacksonville Public Library, 2022.
    - Commencement program, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Caravan literary magazine, 1953 (Box 5)
    - Knight yearbook, 1972 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Class day program, circa late 20th century (Box 5)
  - Edward R. Murrow High School
    - Perspectives yearbook, 1995 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Eli Whitney Vocational High School
    - Torch yearbook, 1963-1965 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Erasmus Hall High School
    Erasmus Hall collection (ARC.230)
    Harriet Oxman Erasmus Hall High School collection (CBHM.0012)
    Art Seidenberg collection of Prospect Park and Erasmus Hall High School postcards (2017.013)
    Isobel Sokolow photographs (V1990.017)
    Lenore Schwartz school records (2017.010)
    Ruth S. Harley family papers (2000.013)
    - The Flying Dutchman yearbook, 1901, 1911, 1920 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      There are four copies of the 1911 issue and two copies of the 1901 and 1920 issues.
    - The Erasmian yearbook, 1898-1902 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - The Arch yearbook, 1934-1959 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1934, June 1935, June 1937, June 1940, June 1941, 1942, 1943, January 1945, June 1946, 1954, 1959
      1937 was the gift of Mark J. Lynn, 2021.
  - Euclid School
    - Promotional materials, 1911 (Box 5)
  - Flatbush School
    - The Annual yearbook, 1922-1924 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      Gift of Sharan Lee Leslie Eastwood.
    - Maroon and White yearbook, June 1924 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Catalog, 1929 (Box 5)
  - Flatbush Village School
    - Flatbush magazine, 1938 (Box 5)
  - Fontbonne Hall
    - Fontbonne yearbook, 1948, 1960, 1961 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - The Folio newspaper, 1958-1960, 1973-1975 (Box 15)
  - Fort Hamilton High School
    - Sonja Kristopherson materials, 1944-1949 (Box 5)
      Valedictory speech, correspondence, recommendation letters, news clippings, 1944 newsletter.
    - The Pilot newspaper, 1959 October (Box 15)
    - Anchor literary magazine, 1961 Spring (Box 5)
    - Tower yearbook, 1945-1997 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The 1945 yearbook was the gift of David Hochman, 2024, and seems to have belonged to Eleanor Powers.
      An obituary for graduate Margaret Ekstrom that originally came with the 1961 yearbook is filed with the school's other materials in Box 5.
      1945, 1947, January 1949, 1961-1970, 1973-1977, 1988, 1995, 1997
    - Brooklyn Lyric Opera program, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Francis Scott Key Junior High School
    - Commencement programs, 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Franklin K. Lane High School
    - Event programs, 1925, 1929, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Image and text regarding new building, circa 1936 (Box 5)
    - Diploma, 1939 (Box 5)
    - Commencement programs, 1939, 1949 (Box 5)
    - The Spook literary magazine, 1940 (Box 5)
    - Senior Echoes yearbook, 1931-1963; Schwarz, Gerard J. (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The January 1949 yearbook was the gift of Mrs. Gerard J. Schwarz, 1986.
      1931, June 1932, January 1935, 1938, January 1939, 1949, 1960-1963
      Schwarz, Gerard J.
    - Women's Army Corps letter, circa 1952 (Box 5)
    - Souvenir booklet, circa 1970s (Box 5)
  - Froebel Academy
    The Froebel Society Records: Brooklyn Chapter (BCMS.0037)
    - Annual report, 1889-1890 (Box 5)
    - Catalog, 1890 (Box 5)
  - George W. Wingate High School
    - Wingate World newspaper, 1970, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Wingate World newspaper, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Alumni and reunion materials, 1986, 1994, 2007; 2022.015 (Box 5)
      Class of 1957.
      Gift of Brian Lane, 2022.
  - George Westinghouse (Vocational) High School
    - Commencement programs, 1964, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Torch yearbook, 1964-2013 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1964-1966, 1969-1970, 1972-1975, 1978-1982, 1984-1986, 1990, 1992-1994, 1999, 2003-2005, 2007, 2009-2010, 2013
    - Westinghouse Reporter publication, January 1960 (Box 6)
  - German American Academy
    - Willie Schroeder examination report, 1887 (Box 6)
    - Alfred and Albert Bode reports, 1888 (Box 6)
      Gift of Elizabeth Feldhusen circa 1989.
  - Girls' Commercial High School
    - Cardinal Notes literary magazine, 1927, 1929, 1931 (Box 6)
    - Commencement programs, 1932 (Box 6)
    - Diploma, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Girls High School
    - Triennial yearbook, 1907, 1910, 1913 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Blue and Gold yearbook, 1915-1930, 1933-1963 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Interlude yearbook, 1934 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Grammar School No. 10
    - Commencement program, 1899 (Box 6)
  - Grammar School No. 12
    - Diploma - Mettie M. Harsen, 1901 (Box 15)
  - Grammar School No. 26
    - Commencement programs, 1877, 1896 (Box 6)
    - Charlotte Morgan report and reward of merit, 1896 (Box 6)
  - Grammar School No. 35
    - Commencement programs, 1892 (Box 6)
    - The School Reporter magazine, 1892-1896 (Box 6)
      Vol. V, No. 1 was the gift of Miss M. Bartlett.
  - Grammar School No. 37
    - Mabel Mahony certificate of promotion, 1899; 1985.048 (Box 15)
      Gift of Vanessa A. Crockford, 1985.
  - Grammar School No. 108
    - Commencement program, 1908 (Box 6)
  - Granberry Piano School
    - Recital program, 1925 (Box 6)
  - Greenleaf Female Institute
    - Catalogs, 1859-1861 (Box 6)
    - Text "Memorabilia of Greenleaf Institute" by Sarah Ball (Box 6)
      Gift of D. Irving Mead.
  - Groschel Conservatory of Music
    - Catalog, 1892-1893 (Box 6)
  - Harrison and Ranney's English and French Boarding and Day School for Young Ladies
    - Catalog, 1867 (Box 6)
  - Harvey's Select School
    - Promotional pamphlet, 1846 (Box 6)
      There is a tuition payment invoice handwritten into the pamphlet.
  - Heffley Institute
    - Promotional materials and student receipt, 1911 (Box 6)
  - Heffley School
    - The Ninth Floor magazine, 1936 April (Box 6)
  - Intermediate School (I.S.) 171K Abraham Lincoln
    - Clarion yearbook, 1992, 1993, 1996-2002, 2005 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - I.S. 218 James Peter Sinnott
    - Commencement program, 1971 (Box 6)
  - I.S. 223 Montauk
    - Wigwam yearbook, 1936, 1952 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - I.S. 252 Arthur S. Somers
    - Principal's album (class photographs), 2001-2002 (Box 6)
    - Yearbook, 1989-1998, 2000-2005, 2007, 2008 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - I.S. 271 John M. Coleman
    - Comet yearbook, 1966-1967 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - I.S. 292 East New York
    - Commencement programs, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
  - I.S. 320 Jackie Robinson
    - Commencement programs, 1973, 1974 (Box 6)
  - James Madison High School
    - The Log/Senior Log yearbook, 1930-2013 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The 1934 yearbook was the gift of Martha Walters, 2025. The 1932 yearbook was the gift of the family of Seymour Silverman.
      1930, 1932, June 1933, 1934-1935, January 1936, 1937-1938, June 1939, 1940, January 1941, June 1942, 1943, January 1945, January 1946, 1948, January 1950, June 1951, 1952, June 1954, 1956, 1959-1961, 1968, 1971, 1974, 1985, 1988-1991, 1993, 1996-1997, 1999, 2000-2001, 2003-2005, 2007, 2009-2013
    - Commencement programs and ticket, 1932, 1934, 1937, 1938, 1950 (Box 6)
      In the June 1950 program, Ruth Bader (later Ruth Bader Ginsburg) is listed among the graduates.
    - Diplomas, 1932, 1934 (Box 6)
    - "M" fabric patch, circa mid-20th century (Box 6)
    - Alumni reunion program, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Jewish National Day Schools - Kinneret
    - Annual banquet materials, 1953 (Box 6)
  - John Dewey High School
    - Brooklyn studies program packet, circa 1980 (Box 6)
  - John Jay High School
    Historical note
    Manual Training High School was renamed John Jay High School in 1960. In 2004, the school closed and its former location is now known as the John Jay Educational Complex.
    - Report card, 1968 (Box 6)
    - Prospect yearbook, 1960-2001 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1960-1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1988, 1990-1992, 1998-2001
    - Library documents, circa 1990s (Box 6)
    - Other documents, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 6)
      Bathroom pass, copy request form, report cards memo.
  - John Marshall Junior High School
    - Commencement program, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Junior High School (J.H.S.) 62 Ditmas
    - The Ditmas Bulletin parents' association newsletter, 1960, 1970 (Box 6)
    - The Ditmas Informer student publication, 1967 (Box 6)
    - Writing institute packet, circa late 20th century (Box 6)
  - J.H.S. 73 William J. Morrison
    - The Comet literary magazine, 1940 January; Schwarz, Gerard J. (Box 6)
      Includes class photographs and honor roll list.
      Gift of Gerard J. Schwarz, 1986.
  - J.H.S. 78 Roy H. Mann
    - Roads of Mann yearbook, 1968; Opis, Scott (Box 6)
      Gift of Scott Opis, 2025.
      Opis, Scott
  - J.H.S. 84 Glenmore
    - Class photographs, 1924, 1937 (Box 15)
      1924 class photo was the gift of Alice Fuchs Garrard, 2018.
    - Autograph book, 1937; 2021.003 (Box 12)
      Gift of William Landau, 2021, along with the class photograph of the same year.
  - J.H.S. 96 Seth Low
    - Autograph book, 1936 January; 2024.030 (Box 12)
      Owned by Seymour Eichel.
      Gift of Trudi Abel, 2024.
    - Spectator literary magazine/yearbook, January 1950, 1998 (Box 6)
  - J.H.S. 128
    - Diploma, 1939 (Box 6)
      Anita Weber.
  - J.H.S. 142 Stranahan
    - Commencement programs, 1973, 1974 (Box 6)
  - J.H.S. 147 Remsen
    - Diploma, 1934 (Box 6)
      Fred Muchnick. Has two pins attached.
  - J.H.S. 149 East New York, 2022.044
    - Perry Goldstein materials, 1938-1941 (Box 6)
      Honorable record certificate, five membership cards and one honor record card.
      See also Goldstein's materials from Thomas Jefferson High School.
    - Vivian Brown materials, 1942-1943 (Box 6)
      Class photograph, commencement program, and three certificates.
      Gift of Ellen W. Ruckstuhl, 2018.
  - J.H.S. 223 Montauk
    - The Mon-Talker parents' association newsletter, 1979 (Box 6)
  - J.H.S. 227 E.B. Shallow
    - The Trumpet yearbook, 1933, 1935, 1938, 1939 (Volume Library gallery shelf, Volume 1933, Box 6)
    - Class photograph, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Shallow Bugle yearbook, 1990 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - J.H.S. 228 David J. Boody
    - Autograph books, 1938, 1939; 2025.001 (Box 12)
      This item belonged to Edith Bartsch and was the gift of Carrie Barlow, 2025.
    - Iris Abramson diploma and autograph book, 1939 (Box 6)
      See also Abramson's items under Abraham Lincoln High School and Brooklyn College.
    - Class photograph, June 1944 (Box 15)
      Gift of Nancy Folchetti-Jacobs, 2025.
    - PTA newsletter, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Beacon yearbook, 1990 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - J.H.S. 232 Winthrop
    - Winthrop Owl, June 1954 and 1957 (Box 7)
      1954 yearbook was the gift of Brian Lane, 2022.
    - Autograph book, 1962 (Box 12)
      Originally owned by Lorraine Diamond and transferred from the Avon Free Public Library in 2025.
    - Event flyer, 1975 (Box 7)
    - The Liberty Bell newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
    - Facts in Five fact sheet, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
    - Press releases and correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - J.H.S. 252 Arthur S. Somers
    - Honor Legion certificate, 1939 (Box 7)
    - Commencement photo album, 1952 (Box 14)
      Includes images of the commencement program and senior prom program.
    - Commencement program, 1955 (Box 7)
    - Drawstring backpack, circa mid 20th century (Box 15)
  - J.H.S. 259 William McKinley
    - Autograph book, 1952 (Box 12)
    - McKinleyan literary magazine, 1958 June (Box 7)
  - J.H.S. 263 David Marcus
    - Groundbreaking ceremony program, 1954 (Box 7)
  - J.H.S. 265 Sands
    - Commencement programs, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1973 (Box 7)
  - J.H.S. 271 John M. Coleman
    - Commencement program, 1967 (Box 7)
  - J.H.S. 296 Halsey
    - Student publications, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      Includes one issue each of Halsey Speaks and Halsey's Many Faces.
  - Kingsborough Community College
    - Event materials, 1968, 1973, 2006-2007 (Box 7)
    - Odyssey yearbook, 1972, 1998 (Box 7, Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Scepter newspaper, 1970-1976 (Box 15)
    - Scepter newspaper, special historical issue, May 10, 1973 (Folder Flat File)
    - Student services handbook and campus map, undated (Box 7)
  - Kings County School of Nursing
    - Student Stripes yearbook, 1941 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      From the estate of Miriam Bloom Tepfer.
    - The First Fifty Years book, 1947 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Kissick's Business Institute
    - Promotional materials, 1911 (Box 7)
  - Lafayette High School
    - Legend yearbook, 1941-2010 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1941, January 1943, 1949, 1951, 1953, 1954, 1956, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1963-1965, 1984-1986, 1990, 1992, 1994-1997, 1999-2010
    - Annual Sing program, 1959 (Box 7)
    - Sheldon Hyman Social Studies exams, circa 1990s-2000s (Box 7)
    - Alumni questionnaire and geographic distribution, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Lafayette Institute
    - Catalogs, 1866-1867, 1868-1869, 1870-1871 (Box 7)
  - Lockwood's New Academy
    - Record, 1871 (Box 7)
    - Testimonial of the Roll of Merit, 1871-1872 (Box 7)
    - Valedictory Address by C.W. Morrow, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Long Island Business College
    - 25th anniversary program, 1898 (Box 7)
  - Long Island College Hospital
    - Catalogue, 1868 (Box 7)
  - Long Island College of Medicine
    - New campus dedication invitation, 1947 (Box 7)
    - Lichonian yearbook, 1948-1949 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Long Island University
    - Sound yearbook, 1948, 1966, 1967, 1992 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - College of Podiatry PodDium yearbook, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Event materials, 1958-2002 (Box 7)
    - Seawanhaka newspaper, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Magazine article "When Blue-Collar Students Go to College", 1972 (Box 7)